Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Squash
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting squash
1956-1995
RU 1033
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, and memos documenting squash at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, and memos documenting squash at Yale.
College athletes; College sports; Squash (Game); Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Records of the squash team, 1956-1995; Accession 2006-A-117
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2030
  - Men's Team
    - General
      - 1956-1957 (Box 1)
      - 1982 (Box 1)
      - 1983 (Box 1)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 1)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Publications, 1979-1995 (Box 1)
  - Women's Team
    - General
      - 1971 (Box 1)
      - 1982 (Box 1)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 1)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 1)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 1)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 1)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 1)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - Post-season, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Search for Women's squash and assistant coach of field hockey or lacrosse, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Publications, 1978-1998 (Box 1)
  - Squash Association, 1981-1989 (Box 2)
    - Board members -Skillman Associates, 1976-1981 (Box 2)
  - Squash court renovation, 1978-1983 (Box 2)
  - Squash tournament, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Photograph of David Huntington with Yale officers, circa 1995 (Box 2)